One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Ordeal
Test
We were tricked!
Tuzağa düşürüldük!
That old lady said it, though. "You can pass."
Yaşlı kadın geçebileceğimizi söylemişti.
And when we do, they say it's illegal entry?!
Şimdi de kaçak olduğumuzu söylüyorlar?!
That's fraud! I'll sue for this!
Sahtekârlık bu! Dava açacağım!
Right...
Evet...
Then again, even if they had said "Don't pass through,"
Gerçi giriş yasak deselerdi,
we would've entered by force anyway.
biz yine zorla girecektik.
Zip it, you!
Konuşma sen!
In any case, you are in big trouble.
Her halükârda, başınız büyük dertte.
Since you've become second-degree criminals,
2. derece suçlu oldunuz artık.
we can't...
Bundan sonra size...
help you.
yardım edemeyiz.
Why are you talking to us from way over there?!
Niye öyle uzaktan konuşuyorsun?!
Well, what's the big deal?
Ne diye büyütüyorsunuz ki?
We're used to being chased.
Peşimizde birilerinin olmasına alışığız.
More importantly, why'd you come back?
Asıl önemli olan, sen neden geri geldin?
Huh?!
Ha?!
We were just about to go to that forbidden place for a big adventu–
Biz de tam o yasaklı yere macer–
Uh... I-I mean, to look for you!
Ah...Y-Yani seni aramaya geliyorduk!
You're really easy to figure out.
Senin ciğerini bilirim ben.
Were you about to say "big adventure"?!
Ne macerası be?!
Didn't I tell you already?!
Demedim mi ben size?!
You're only saying that because you haven't seen
Hâlâ macera diyorsun çünkü...
how terrifying the people on that island are!
o adadaki tiplerin ne kadar korkunç olduğunu görmedin!
We don't know much about this God guy,
Şu Tanrı denen herifin ne ayak olduğunu bilmesek de doğaüstü güçleri olduğu kesin!
I will never go back...
O adaya asla...
to that island!
geri dönmem!
Then, you can just wait here while we go.
O hâlde bizi burada bekleyebilirsin.
No way! I'll get arrested!
Olmaz! Beni bulup tutuklarlar!
We have to leave this place!
Buradan gitmeliyiz!
Leave?! Are you nuts?!
Gitmeli miyiz?! Kafayı mı yedin?!
Which is more important to you, adventure or life?!
Hangisi senin için daha önemli? Macera mı hayat mı?
Life! Then money!
Hayat! Sonra da para!
Oh?! And next would be me?!
Ah?! Ardından da ben miyim?!
Shut it!
Kes!
But it's true.
Aslında doğru.
Y'know, we were trying so desperately to reach the sky island that
Düşününce gökyüzü adasına ulaşmak için o kadar uğraştık...
how we'd get home never even crossed our minds.
ve nasıl geri döneceğimizi hiç düşünmedik bile.
Say, is there a way for us to get back safely?
Geri dönmenin güvenli bir yolu var mı ki?
Can we return to the Blue Sea?
Mavi Deniz'e geri dönebilecek miyiz?
I can't say that it's safe, but there is a way...
Güvenli olduğunu söyleyemem ama bulutların en uc noktasında,
at the farthest edge of the clouds, Cloud End.
Bulutun Sonu denilen bir yol var.
Cloud End? How do we get there?
Bulutun Sonu mu? Oraya nasıl gidebiliriz?
Cloud End is far to the east.
Bulutun Sonu doğu tarafında.
To get there, you need to go down to the White Sea first.
Oraya gitmek için önce Beyaz Deniz'e inmeniz gerekiyor.
Great! Then, we can get back to our sea from there, right?
Güzel! Oradan bizim dünyamıza dönebiliriz değil mi?
No way! I'm not going back!
Olmaz! Geri dönmeyeceğim!
Hey, would you rather get the death sentence here?
Hey, burada kalıp idam edilmeyi mi tercih edersin?
In any case, staying here will cause trouble for Conis and her dad.
Unutma, burada kalırsak Conis ve babasının da başını derde sokarız.
Oh, it's no trouble...
Ah, bizi düşünmeyin lütfen...
Well, even if we run away, they'll probably find us.
Kaçsak bile muhtemelen bizi bulacaklardır.
That means it'll be the same wherever we go in Skypiea.
Yani Skypiea'nın neresine gitsek, durum aynı.
Since they know our location, we'd better leave right away!
Nerede olduğumuzu biliyorlar, bir an önce gitsek iyi olur!
Now, everyone! Let's set sail!
Hadi millet! Gidelim!
Conis! Mister! Thanks for everything!
Conis! Bayım! Her şey için teşekkürker!
Oh, yeah!
Ah, evet!
Let's go, Luffy!
Gidelim, Luffy!
Hey, old guy!
Hey, ihtiyar!
What is it?
Ne oldu?
Can I take all the leftover food from earlier with me?
Yemeklerden kalanları alabilir miyim?
Yes, of course.
Evet, tabii.
Alright! Sanji, prepare some lunch boxes!
Pekâlâ! Sanji, gel de yolluk hazırla bize!
No food gets by you.
Senden de yemek kaçmıyor.
In that case, can I ask you a favor as well?
Bu arada ben de bir şey isteyebilir miyim?
You're an engineer, right, old guy?
İhtiyar, sen mühendistin, değil mi?
Would you give me some spare parts for the ship repairs?
Gemiye yama yapmalık yedek parçan var mı hiç?
Sure, I don't see why not. Then, let's go to the house again.
Evet, tabii. Eve gidip bakalım.
Hold on! Where are you guys going?!
Durun! Nereye gidiyorsunuz?!
I'm gonna get some food from them!
Yemek alıp geleceğiz!
Men! Go ahead and prepare the ship for adventure!
Siz gemiyi yeni maceralar için hazırlayın!
He's definitely planning on going there.
Kesin o yasak yere gitme planları yapıyor.
They really were scary!
Onlar cidden korkutucuydu!
Who cares?! Makes no difference to me.
Kimin umurunda?! Benim için fark etmez.
It's not my choice, anyway.
Sinirini benden çıkarma.
Chopper, you're on my side, aren't you?!
Chopper, sen benim tarafımdasın, değil mi?!
– What?! – Don't force him!
– Ne?! – Zorlama onu!
Heavy Point!
Ağırlık Noktası!
I was about to drop a rope ladder.
Tam da merdiveni salacaktım.
Oops.
Pardon.
You realize that there's no persuading Luffy, don't you?
Luffy'i ikna etmenin bir yolu yok, biliyorsun değil mi?
Even if we all protest, he won't listen.
Hepimiz karşı çıksak bile dinlemez.
Fine! I won't go, then.
Öyle olsun! Ben burada kalacağım.
Hm? So be it, then.
Ha? Nasıl istersen.
"So be it"?!
"Nasıl istersen" mi?!
Hey, I'll be killed by those jerks!
Hey, o garip tipler gelip beni öldürecek!
Ah? Then so be it.
Eh? N'apalım öyle olsun.
Why you...!
Ulan...!
Robin...
Robin...
why don't you and I take down Luffy?
neden ikimiz Luffy'i benzetip ikna etmiyoruz?
That's absurd.
Olmaz öyle.
I guess we've got a better chance at taking on those jerks, huh?
Bizi almaya gelecek tiplere karşı şansımız daha fazla değil mi?
Those White Berets must be regrouping to come after us now.
O Beyaz Bereliler bizi almak için hazırlanıyorlardır şimdi.
Come after you? How foolish!
Sizi almak mı? Ne büyük ahmaklık!
God and his priests are as immovable as mountains.
Tanrı ve rahipleri dağ gibi hareketsizlerdir.
They lie in wait on sacred ground while the judged come their way.
Kutsal yerde hükümlülerin ayaklarına gelmesini beklerler.
Once you weigh anchor, your ordeal will start.
Yelken açtığınız anda test edileceksiniz.
You'll be led to...
Yasak yer olan...
the forbidden sacred ground...
Yukarı Bahçe'ye...
Upper Yard!
yönlendirileceksiniz!
This is tasty!
Bu çok lezzetliymiş!
Hey, don't eat our lunch!
Hey, öğle yemeğimizi yeme!
There's a lot, so don't hold back.
Çok var, o yüzden elini korkak alıştırma.
You're the one who should hold back.
Elini korkak alıştırması gereken kişi sensin.
Conis, gimme some tea!
Conis, biraz çay koy!
Do it yourself!
Kalk kendin al!
Oh? Conis isn't here.
Ah? Conis-chan burada değil.
Looks like she went to bid a fond farewell to the others.
Görünüşe göre diğerlerine veda etmeye gitti.
Here is the tea.
Buyurun çay.
So, you're the crew's shipwright?
Gemi marangozu musun?
What? No, I'm not. I'm a marksman.
Ne? Hayır değilim. Keskin nişancıyım.
Oh, how fascinating!
Ah, ne güzel!
Right? Our ship still doesn't have a shipwright.
Değil mi? Gemi marangozumuz henüz yok.
Since I'm an almighty jack of all trades, everyone depends on me!
Her derde deva, marifetli bir dâhi olduğum için herkesin bana güveni tam!
It's a lot of work.
Yorucu bir iş.
That ship just wouldn't function without me.
O gemi ben olmadan gitmez.
I'm not just the marksman, it's like I'm also co-captain.
Sadece keskin nişancı değil, aynı zamanda ikinci kaptanım.
So everyone calls me: Captain Usopp!
O yüzden herkes bana Kaptan Usopp der!
Oh, dear! This color arrangement is clearly done by a professional!
Vay be! Bu renk uyumu... Apaçık bir profesyonelin eseri!
Of course! Food arrangement is art.
Elbette öyle! Yemek sunumu da bir sanattır.
No, this is in the wrong place.
Yok, bunun yeri olmadı.
I put the red one there, and put the emerald green broad beans here.
Kırmızı olanı buraya, zümrüt yeşili fasulyeleri de buraya koyayım.
Now they look even tastier!
Şimdi daha iyi görünüyor.
One for my sweet Nami and one for my lovely Robin.
Bir tane Nami-san'a, bir tane de Robin-chan'a.
Wow, who could eat such works of art!
Vay, insan bunları yemeye kıyamaz!
No, thank you. I'm sorry.
Hayır, teşekkürler. Özür dilerim.
I've never seen such a pretty lunch before.
Hiç böyle güzel bir yemek görmemiştim.
Really?
Cidden mi?
This is for you, Conis.
Bu senin için, Conis-chan.
Oh?! You made one for me, too?!
Oh?! Bana da mı yaptın?!
Of course! The title of this lunch is...
Tabii ki! Bu yemeğin ismi...
"Love is a dilemma. Lunch for the fallen angel."
"Meleğe gönül kaptırıp düşülen aşk çıkmazı."
Oh...
Ah...
Well, once it's in your stomach,
Ama yedikten sonra...
it's all the same.
hepsi aynı.
Don't say stuff that tears down my hard work!
Emeklerimi küçümseyen şeyler söyleme!
Listen up! With food, presentation comes first!
Bak dinle! Yemeklerin sunumu çok önemlidir!
Really?
Öyle mi?
See? No difference.
Bak? Hiçbir farkları yok.
Don't chow them down without even looking!
Bakmadan ağzına tıkıyorsun!
Why not?
N'apim?
It all tastes the same, too.
Hepsinin tadı aynı sonuçta.
Like I said, eat them with your eyes first!
Önce yemeği gözlerinle yemelisin!
That's dumb. Eyes can't eat food!
Öyle şey mi olur. Ben bile gözlerimle yemek yiyemem!
Hmm?
Hmm?
Hey! Something's wrong with the ship!
Hey! Gemide bir problem var!
What?!
Ne?!
What's going on, Usopp?!
Ne oluyor, Usopp?!
Look at that! The ship's rocking!
Baksanıza! Gemi sallanıyor!
A party? No fair, having a party without us!
Parti mi yapıyorlar? Hem de bizsiz!
Ah! Nami!
Ah! Nami-san!
Why...
Neden...
Why is she wearing a t-shirt?!
Neden tişört giyiyor?!
Just where the heck is your mind at?!
Aklın nerede lan?!
Ahh! The ship started moving!
Ahh! Gemi gidiyor!
What?! Why?!
Ne?! Neden?!
What're they doing? Where're they going?
Ne yapıyorlar? Nereye gidiyorlar?
Whoa! It's moving backward! That's incredible!
Oha! Geri geri gidiyor! İnanılmaz!
That's not it! It's not moving on its own!
Hayır, iyi bak! Kendi kendine gitmiyor!
Huh?
Ha?
Look underneath the ship!
Geminin altına bak!
Hold on! What is this?! What's going on?!
Durun bi'! Bu ne böyle?! Neler oluyor?!
That's...
Bu...
the famous White-White Sea superexpress lobster!
Beyaz-Beyaz Deniz'in ünlü süper ıstakoz ekspresi!
It's trying to take us somewhere!
Bizi bir yere götürmeye çalışıyor!
Hey! Everyone off the ship! There's still time!
Hey! Herkes gemiden insin! Hâlâ vakit var!
What about the ship?! If our ship is taken...
Peki ya gemi ne olacak?! Eğer gemimizi alırlarsa...
Don't worry. I'll stay.
Endişelenmeyin. Ben kalacağım.
C'mon! What can you do by yourself?!
Saçmalama! Tek başına ne yapacaksın ki?!
I'll figure it out!
Bir çaresine bakarım!
Alright, this'll work!
Hallettim gibi!
Unfortunately, that'd be useless.
Sanki işe yaramadı.
Come on board!
Gemiye geri gel!
What'd you say?!
Ne dedin?!
Even if that works, we'll just play right into their next move. Look.
İşe yarasa bile dahası var. Bak!
What?!
Ne?!
Large sky fish are following us with their mouths open.
Dev gökyüzü balıkları peşimizde.
We can't jump off the ship to escape, now.
Gemiden inip kaçamayız.
Even if we defeat them, others would likely take their place.
Onların icabına baksak bile muhtemelen daha fazlası gelecektir.
There's nothing we can do. It's probably already started.
Yapabileceğimiz bir şey yok. Muhtemelen çoktan başladı.
Divine Reckoning, huh?
İlahi Adalet, ha?
Instead of sending people after us, he's bringing us to them.
Peşimize adam takmak yerine bizi kendilerine çekiyorlar.
He's got some nerve.
Yüzsüz herifler...
Then... I'm going back to that island?
Yani... O adaya geri mi gidiyorum?
Luffy! Usopp! Sanji!
Luffy! Usopp! Sanji-kun!
Why...? Why a t-shirt...?
Neden...? Neden tişört...?
You're still stuck on that?!
Hâlâ ona mı takıldın?!
Hey, Luffy! This is terrible! What do we do?! What do we do?!
Hey, Luffy! Bu çok fena! Ne yapacağız?! Ne yapacağız?!
Where'd they go?
Nereye gittiler ki?
Of course, they... Huh?!
Onlar tabii ki... Ha?!
So where?
Nereye?
Where...
Onlar...
...did they...
...nereye...
...go?
...gitti?
The superexpress lobster is a messenger of God.
Süper ıstakoz ekspresi, Tanrı'nın ulağıdır.
What it transports is always an offering to God.
Tanrı'ya kurban edilecekleri taşır.
So, it's headed to northeast Upper Yard...
Yukarı Bahçe'nin kuzeydoğusuna gidiyor...
to the sacrificial altar.
adakların götürüldüğü sunağa.
Sacrificial altar?! Nami, Robin, and the rest...
Adak mı?! Nami-san, Robin-chan ve diğerleri...
The rest?!
Ne demek diğerleri?!
...will be sacrificed?!
...kurban mı edilecek?!
For that damn god?!
O lanet olası Tanrı'ya?!
That son of a bitch!
Şerefsiz herif!
Don't mess with us, you bastard!
Bize nasıl bulaşır, piç herif!
Hold on a second, please!
Lütfen, dur biraz!
But, I'm sorry! That's not the case!
Tam olarak öyle değil, özür dilerim!
What?!
Ne?!
While it can all be considered a sacrifice,
Kurban edilme dense bile,
with Divine Reckoning, criminals receive one of two punishments.
aslında İlahi Adalet suçluları iki cezadan birine çarptırılırlar.
Either a sacrifice or an ordeal.
Kurban edilme ya da zorlu bir test.
They're currently hostages in God's hands, so to speak.
Aslında tam olarak Tanrı'nın elinde rehinler şu an.
Hostages?!
Rehin mi?!
So, the ones who are actually being judged...
Yani aslında şu anda yargılananlar...
are the three of you.
siz üçünüzsünüz.
Huh? What do you mean?
Ha? Ne diyorsun sen?
If only I had a map...
Bir haritam olaydı da...
Oh, I actually have a map of Skypiea with me.
Ah, aslında yanımda bir Skypiea haritası var.
It's fairly outdated, isn't it?
Bu epey eski.
But the shape of the island seems correct.
Ancak adanın şekli doğru.
This is where you are right now.
Şu anda buradasınız.
The sacrificial altar is up and to the left, northeast.
Adak sunağı solda yukarıda, kuzeydoğu yönünde.
To get there, only one route is available.
Oraya gitmenin tek bir yolu var.
Using a dial boat, take the milky road from this island,
Dial botu kullanarak bu adadan süt yoluna sapıp,
and cross over to the forest where the priests await you.
rahiplerin sizi beklediği adayı geçmelisiniz.
Well, old guy,
Peki ihtiyar,
instead of winding our way through the island,
adanın içinden geçmek yerine...
all we have to do is go around it by boat, right?
neden botumuzla çevresinden dolaşmıyoruz?
That lobster went to Upper Yard that way, too, didn't it?
O ıstakoz da Yukarı Bahçe'ye o şekilde gitmedi mi?
Well...
Şey...
even if you make landfall near the altar, it's inaccessible by foot.
Sunağın olduğu yere botla yanaşsanız bile oraya yayan çıkamazsınız.
This map is far different from today's Upper Yard,
Bu haritanın gösterdiğiyle günümüzün Yukarı Bahçe'si epey farklı,
because milky roads now stretch all around the island.
çünkü sütlü yollar artık adanın her yerine ulaşıyor.
Those are the cloud canals, right?
Şu bulut kanalını mı diyorsun?
Yes. I hear that there are several hundred milky roads,
Evet. Duyduğuma göre orada irili ufaklı,
large and small in size, over there.
yüzlerce "Süt Yolu" varmış.
Hmm... I see...
Hmm... Anladım...
That is why entering the island by boat
Bu yüzden adaya botla girmek ve...
and taking the milky roads within is the only way.
sütlü yolları takip etmek tek yol.
I see.
Anladım.
So no matter where we try to dock, the canals will block our way.
Yani nereye yanaşırsak yanaşalım, kanallar yolumuzu tıkayacak.
That's right.
Aynen öyle.
By the way, there are also man-eating fish in the canals.
Bu arada kanallarda insan yiyen balıklar var.
Man-eating fish?!
İnsan yiyen balık mı?!
They've really covered all their bases.
Resmen her köşe başını tutmuşlar!
So, in order to get our friends and ship back,
Yani arkadaşlarımızı ve gemimizi geri almak için,
we just have to come in from the front.
tek yapmamız gereken ön kapıdan dalmak!
So that's our ordeal... and Divine Reckoning?!
Demek bizi bekleyen test bu... İlahi Adalet ha?
Yes. Four unimaginably strong priests await you in Upper Yard.
Evet. Yukarı Bahçe'de sizi, akıl almaz derecede güçlü dört rahip beklemekte.
That's it? Sounds easy to me.
Bu kadar mı? Epey kolaymış.
In other words, all we have to do is beat up those priests, right?
Kısacası gidip o rahipleri dövmemiz gerekiyor, değil mi?
You're so simple-minded.
Amma düz adamsın.
This is getting fun!
İşte eğlence şimdi başlıyor!
Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Upper Yard Lovely Street Angel Beach
Sevimli Cadde Melek Sahili Yukarı Bahçe
Wow! This place is great!
Vay be! Burası harika!
Lovely Street is Angel Island's only shopping center.
Sevimli Cadde, Melek Adası'nın en canlı yeridir.
Check it out! The stores are floating!
Baksanıza! Dükkânlar havada duruyor!
They're built using the special properties of island clouds.
Hepsi, ada bulutlarının özel olarak işlenmesiyle yapıldı.
Wow! Any barbecue shops?
Vay! Et lokantası var mı burada?
Is it just me, or is everyone avoiding us?
Bana mı öyle geliyor yoksa insanlar bizden uzak mı duruyor?
Can't blame 'em.
Onları suçlayamam.
Word's probably gotten out that we're criminals.
Suçlu olduğumuzun dedikodusu yayılmış olmalı.
This feels great!
Bu harika!
We've got the whole place to ourselves!
Bütün cadde bize kaldı!
All the angels are avoiding me...
Bütün melekler benden kaçıyor.
Oh? There sure is a lot of weird stuff for sale!
Ah? Amma garip şeyler satıyorlar!
This one's nice! Too bad I'm broke. Is a treasure payment plan okay?
Ne güzel! Keşke alacak param olsaydı. Deftere yazdırsak oluyor mu?
No, no!
Hayır!
Luffy! This isn't the time to be fooling around!
Luffy! Oyalanacak zamanımız yok!
Nami's group will be sacrificed!
Nami-san ve diğerleri kurban edilecekler!
Do you even want to save them?!
Onları kurtarmak istemiyor musun?!
Save them? They're gonna be fine! Zoro was caught with them!
Kurtarmak mı? Onlara bir şey olmaz! Zoro da onlarla!
Like we can really count on him!
Sanki ona güvenebilirmişiz gibi!
With how crazy things have been, I hope the ship is still in one piece.
Umarım onca kargaşadan sonra gemi hâlâ tek parçadır.
Huh?! There's something in the street!
Ha?! Caddenin ortasında bir şey var!
Huh?
Ha?
What a weird face! What is this? A seal?
Ne garip suratı var! Bu ne? Fok mu?
Some kind of weird mud figure, so maybe it's a religious statue?
Tuhaf bir çamurdan figür... Put olabilir mi?
Morons! This is art! I can tell!
Aptallar! Sanat bu! Anlarım ben!
It's "vearth."
O "Vearth".
The people of the sky have always admired it.
Gökyüzü insanları ona hep büyük hayranlık duymuştur.
"Vearth"?
"Vearth" mü?
What? You guys admire this thing? You must be crazy...
Ne? Buna mı hayranlık duyuyorsunuz? Kafayı yediniz herhâlde...
Yes, I'm sure it must be difficult for Blue Sea people to understand.
Evet, eminim bu Mavi Deniz insanı için anlaması zor bir durum.
Oh, the docks are this way!
Ah, rıhtım bu tarafta!
What? We're leaving town already?!
Ne? Hemen ayrılıyor muyuz?!
What are you talking about?! We have somewhere to be!
Ne diyorsun be?! Yapmamız gerekenler var!
Would it hurt to hang around a little longer?
Hadi ama biraz daha dolansak olmaz mı?
– Whoa!
– Vay!
So many boats!
Ne kadar çok bot var!
There are all kinds of boats anchored here.
Burada her tür bot var.
Whoa! Check out this gondola!
Vay! Şu gondola bakın!
It's so cool! Let's borrow it!
Çok havalı! Hadi ödünç alalım şunu!
Look behind it! This one can move on its own, like a waver!
Arkasına bakın! Waver gibi kendi hareket edebilen modellerden biri!
I smell a fun gondola adventure!
Eğlenceli bir gondol turu olur gibi!
We're rescuing Nami and Robin, you idiot! Get serious!
Seni aptal! Nami-san ve Robin-chan'ı kurtarmaya gidiyoruz! Biraz ciddi ol!
Oh, your boat is over here.
Sizin botunuz burada.
Right!
Peki!
– Oh?!
– Öyle mi?!
Oh, boy! What kind of gondola is it?!
Acaba bizimkisi nasıl bir gondol?!
The Little Crow!
Küçük Karga!
You can't be serious!
Dalga geçiyorsun herhâlde!
Crows...
Kargaların...
aren't even waterfowl.
suyla alakası bile yok.
I used it until recently, when I learned how to ride wavers.
Waver sürmeyi öğrenmeden önce hep bunu kullandım.
It's not as fast as a waver, but it does run on two breath dials.
Waver kadar hızlı değil ama iki breath dial'ı var.
Please feel free to use it!
Buyrun çekinmeden kullanın!
No... I'm not going.
Yok... Ben gitmiyorum.
Just as I expected!
Aynen beklediğim gibi!
He shows his true colors at the last minute!
Asıl rengini son anda belli etti!
I wanna use that one instead.
Ben onu istiyorum.
It was just about the ship?
Derdi bot muymuş?
Y-You don't like it? I'm sorry. But...
B-Bunu sevmedin mi? Özür dilerim. Ama...
You damn ingrate! Apologize!
Pis nankör! Özür dile!
Apologize to Conis from the bottom of your heart, you scumbag!
Conis-chan'dan samimi bir şekilde özür dile, şerefsiz seni!
Pay no attention to his selfishness!
Bunun küstahlığına bakma sen!
Sorry!
Özür dilerim!
Yes...
Peki...
Your exit is gate number two.
2 numaralı kapıdan çıkacaksınız.
It will lead you to a giant milky road, which connects to Upper Yard.
Sizi Yukarı Bahçe'ye götürecek büyük süt yoluna çıkacaksınız.
Th-The route is as simple as that.
R-Rota bu kadar basit.
Hey, Conis.
Hey, Conis.
Yes?
Evet?
Why have you been shaking ever since we left your house?
Evinden ayrıldığımızdan beri neden titriyorsun?
Wh-What the hell is he saying?!
Ne diyor bu?!
D-Does it seem that way?
T-Titriyor muyum?
Yeah. It's like you're afraid of something...
Evet. Sanki bir şeyden korkuyor gibisin...
No! Is she...?
Olamaz! Yoksa...?
Conis! You're worried about us! That's so touching!
Conis-chan! Bizim için endişeleniyor musun?! Bu çok hoş!
Still, are you and your father gonna be okay?!
Sen ve baban, iyi olacak mısınız?!
Everyone in town is obviously avoiding us,
Bütün şehir bizden uzak duruyor,
yet you're lending us your boat and even giving us directions...
ama sen, bize botunu ödünç verip üstüne de yolu tarif ediyorsun...
Doesn't that make you our accomplices?
Bu seni suç ortağı yapmaz mı?
You're looking real pale, too...
Rengin soluk görünüyor...
You should've told us if you were that scared.
Eğer korkuyorsan baştan söyleseydin keşke.
We would've come here on our own...
Kendi başımıza gelirdik...
No.
Hayır.
I'm...
Ben...
It's not what you think!
Düşündüğünüz gibi değil!
She wouldn't!
Yapamaz!
Don't say anything you shouldn't!
Sakın ağzını açma!
It is strange, isn't it?
Tuhaf, değil mi?
Explaining the route to your ordeal, guiding you here myself...
Sizi buraya kadar kendim getirip üstüne yolu tarif etmem...
It's like I want to lead you there, despite saying how terrifying it is...
Yolun korkunçluğunu anlattığım hâlde ısrarla sizi oraya yönlendirmem...
Stop it! Don't say something you'll regret!
Dur! Sakın pişman olacağın bir şey söyleme!
Huh? What was that?
Ha? O kimdi?!
Don't tell me they're all...
Sakın bana hepsinin...
It is our citizens' duty. It is his will.
Bu, halkın görevi. Hepsi onun isteği.
Could you run away?
Neden kaçmadınız ki?
I'm so sorry!
Çok özür dilerim!
Stop!
Dur!
What are you saying?!
Ne diyorsun sen?!
I was the one who called the superexpress lobster!
Süper ıstakoz ekpresini çağıran bendim!
The thing that took Nami and the others?!
Nami-san ve diğerlerini götüren şeyi mi diyorsun?!
You called it?!
Sen mi çağırdın?!
While you were back at the house,
Siz evdeyken onlara,
I lied to them about a current that leads to Cloud End
Bulutun Sonu'na giden bir akıntı var diye yalan söyledim...
and had them raise the anchor.
ve bu yüzden demir aldılar.
That was the signal for the superexpress lobster.
Bu, süper ıstakoz ekspresinin beklediği sinyaldi!
Foolish girl! Do you want to die?!
Ahmak kız! Canına mı susadın?!
This is our duty!
Bizim görevimiz bu!
Once we know someone's a criminal,
Bir suçluyu bilip de...
we'll be killed if we don't lead them to the place of reckoning!
onu yargılanacağı yere yönlendirmezsek cezası ölüm olur!
Stop it! Do you realize what you're saying?!
Dursana! Ne dediğini farkında mısın?!
That's blasphemy!
Yaptığın günah!
Stop her!
Durdurun onu!
This is our duty as citizens.
Halk olarak buna zorunluyuz...
Are you serious?!
Sen ciddi misin?!
I'm sorry!
Özür dilerim!
It's all so strange, isn't it?!
Çok tuhaf, değil mi?!
Don't be stupid! You didn't have any choice, right?!
Aptal olma! Başka şansın yoktu, değil mi?!
So then...
O zaman...
– ...why are you telling us?!
– ...niye bize söyledin?!
Your life is in danger!
Şimdi başın belada!
It's all over!
İş işten geçti!
We're too late!
Çok geç kaldık!
Stay away from the girl!
Kızdan uzak durun!
Reckoning is coming!
Ceza geliyor!
No good! It's too big!
Kaçamayacağız! Çok büyük!
What was that?!
O neydi?!
What just happened?!
Ne oldu öyle?!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Conis! Hey! Where'd you go?!
Conis-chan! Hey! Nereye gittiniz?!
Luffy! Conis!
Luffy! Conis!
It's no use...
Faydası yok...
The almighty God Enel sees all...!
Yüce Tanrı Enel her şeyi görür...!
They are both safe.
Güvendeler.
It's Gan Fall!
Gan Fall-san!
Hey, it's that old weirdo!
Oh, tuhaf ihtiyar!
"Weirdo"?
"Tuhaf" mı?
No, I am the Sky Knight! This one is on the house!
Lütfen bana Gökyüzü Şövalyesi deyin! Bu benden olsun!
Thank goodness! Conis...!
Şükürler olsun! Conis-chan...!
Leave this girl with me. I will not allow Enel to harm her.
Bu kızı bana bırakın. Enel'in ona zarar vermesine izin vermeyeceğim.
Good!
Olur!
You now know this land's true nature, as well as God's power.
Artık bu adada işlerin nasıl yürüdüğünü biliyorsunuz, Tanrı'nın gücünü de gördünüz.
What will you do now?
Şimdi ne yapacaksınız?
I don't care what happens to this place.
Burada ne olduğu umurumda değil.
Our friends are on God's Island.
Arkadaşlarımız Tanrı'nın Adası'nda!
I see... May luck be with you.
Anladım... Şans yanınızda olsun.
What about them?
Peki onlar?
They have chosen their course.
Onlar seçimini yaptı.
It is no fault of yours.
Senin bir suçun yok.
I know who you are.
Senin kim olduğunu biliyorum.
I am the Sky Knight.
Ben Gökyüzü Şövalyesi'yim.
No, we all know. Please come back...
Hayır, hepimiz biliyoruz. Lütfen geri dönün...
God!
Tanrı'm!
Get on! I'll give you a strong push out!
Atlayın! Güçlüce iteceğim!
You're coming, too!
Sen de geliyorsun!
Alright, let's go to Upper Yard!
Pekâlâ, hadi Yüksek Bahçe'ye gidelim!
No...!
Hayır...!
The bastards actually left...
Şerefsizler harbiden gidiyor...
with no hesitation or uncertainty at all.
hem de hiç tereddüt etmeden.